Later,
let it keep you company.
This is...
The exact same
sleeping doll from back then.
But when you were little,
why did you always like holding this doll?
[Dearest Episode 11]
That was a sleeping doll Wen Xin gave me.
Back when she still acted like a mother,
she would always comfort me
to sleep with this doll.
So much so that later, without it,
I couldn't even sleep.
Let it stay with you
for the rest of this journey
in my place.
Thank you.
Jiang Yu.
Be careful.
♪ Holding tightly to my hands and scars ♪
♪ Your deep breathing ♪
♪ Guided like the stars ♪
♪ Now I'll never let you go ♪
♪ At the edge of this breaking world ♪
Go
♪ You are the only one
who brought the light ♪
♪ Because it's you ♪
♪ All my sorrows ♪
♪ Fading out of sight ♪
♪ In your arms, I'm born again and new ♪
♪ All the cruel darkness fades away ♪
♪ And you bring the colors of the day ♪
♪ I will stay by your side ever-more ♪
♪ The only one who brought me through ♪
♪ Because it's you. ♪
Something's wrong.
Jianan.
Don't let her live.
You handle it.
Your leader was bought off by Jiang Yu.
Work with me,
and you will be the new leader.
Please go. I'll handle things here.
What a perfect face
and such healthy vitals.
Mr. He actually wants to
dispose of you on the spot.
What a waste!
Don't worry.
I have a client
who likes exactly your type.
Rare blood type,
fresh parts.
Before we take you apart and ship you off,
we have plenty of time
to take good care of you.
Go away!
Let her go!
You got here fast enough.
Mr. He clearly underestimated you.
But...
This is my place.
You can get in
but never get out in a snake pit.
Get him!
Jiang Yu!